myshopping.com.au 2019-11-20

# MyShopping.com.au Privacy Policy

| 

Nov 16th, 2017

## Maintaining your privacy

MyShopping Australial Pty Ltd owns and operates this site 'MyShopping'. We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to maintaining the privacy and accuracy of your personal information. We take all reasonable precautions to ensure the personal information we collect, use and disclose is accurate and current. However, the accuracy of that information depends largely on the information you provide. Privacy of children This site is not directed at or intended for use by persons under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect, store or disclose personal information of persons under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please immediately exit from the site and do not use or access this site unless and until we receive verified parental consent for your continued use. We will take relevant action to delete the personal information of persons under the age of 13 where we learn such information has been collected and stored through the site without verified parental consent. 

## Collecting personal information

MyShopping collects aggregated, non-personal statistical information on site visitors such as: 

  * your server IP address
  * the date and time of your visit to the site
  * the pages you accessed and the documents downloaded
  * the duration of your visit to the site
  * the previous site you have visited
  * the type of web browser you are using
  * other information provided by your browser's HTTP headers

MyShopping also collects user submitted information such as:

  * MyShopping rewards program account information, including name and email address; 
  * location information, including city, state and postcode
  * reviews, articles, responses, opinion and ratings of merchants, stores, products and services
  * rewards program membership details

Please note, when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information on the MyShopping site via reviews, messages, forums or postings, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can potentially be collected, correlated and used by third parties. 

## Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information sent to your browser to authenticate, track, and maintain specific information about your interactions with a site. MyShopping uses cookies to remember who you are when you log-in, to tracking your browsing patterns and to customise and improve our site. The type of information we collect depends on what information and services you access and use, but generally do not contain or are not tied to your personal information. We may also use cookies for anonymous profiling purposes to tailor advertising to your preferences. You may opt-out of this anonymous profiling by contacting us. You can instruct your browser to refuse cookies, although this may prevent access to or limit some of the information of services contained on the site. 

## MyShopping Rewards Program Registration

If you wish to access and use MyShopping Rewards Program, you must register and create a user account. All information you provide when registering for a MyShopping Rewards Program user account including your name, address, email address, telephone number or other details can be viewed, modified or deleted at any time by contacting us or by accessing the "MyShopping Rewards Program" section of the site. Registered users who wish to close their account should send an email to contactus@myshopping.com.au. If requested, MyShopping will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally remove your personal information from the site. Given the nature of the MyShopping site, it may be impossible to remove all details and some residual personal information may remain on the site. 

## Using personal information

MyShopping is an online environment that allows people to compare merchants, products, stores and prices. All of this information is aggregated and made available in a convenient form. To accomplish this, some users write reviews, articles, opinions or responses about merchants, products, stores and prices and post this information to the site. These postings can then be accessed and read by other MyShopping users. To fulfil this purpose of the site, we need to display a limited amount of personal information, so that users are able to evaluate the trustworthiness of a particular contribution. MyShopping does not use or disclose your personal information for a purpose other than that for which it was collected, unless such use or disclosure would be reasonably expected or, if you give us your consent. In the event that you opt in for surveys or [complete surveys](https://www.rewardia.com.au/Paid-Surveys-How-it-Works?pk=lp), your personal information may be collected and used for research, validation, de-duplication or specific project needs by our Affiliate or partners. You also consent to your information being transferred outside Australia by our partners and affiliates. Unless you contact us to indicate otherwise, you consent to your personal information being used to: 

  * establish a MyShopping Rewards Program user account
  * contact you for any purpose related to your account or your use of the site
  * verify your identity
  * market products, services and special offers to you
  * assist you to subscribe to any newsletter or other promotions we offer or may in the future offer and to manage and administer those services
  * make changes to your profile
  * respond to any queries or feedback you may have
  * inform you of ways the information or services provided to you could be improved
  * research and develop our services
  * to being disclosed to a partner or affiliate for marketing and research purposes
  * maintain and develop our business systems
  * display and aggregate your postings, including ratings, opinions, articles, comments and reviews
  * allow other users of the site to contact or send postings and messages to you
  * gain a better understanding of your information service requirements
  * facilitate an individual's participation in a rewards program
  * facilitate an individual's redemptions through a rewards program
  * conduct appropriate checks for credit-worthiness or fraud

If you complete [online surveys](https://www.rewardia.com.au/), your information may be transferred to our affiliates and partners who are independent entities. We therefore recommend that you read their user agreement and privacy statement before providing us with any of your details. 

Several advertising networks are responsible for placing some of the advertising on this site. To make this advertising more relevant to you, anonymous information about the previous web browsing activity of your computer is collected and used to associate your computer with one or more pre-defined interest categories. Advertising that matches those interest categories may then be served to your computer. This interest based advertising does not change the amount of advertising you receive, it just makes it more relevant. General information about interest based advertising is available from the industry website www.youronlinechoices.com.au 

## Transferring your personal information

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of MyShopping, such as an acquisition by or merger with another company. In such an event, MyShopping will notify you (by displaying a notice in your MyShopping Rewards Program user account) before your personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. MyShopping will notify you (by displaying a notice in your MyShopping Rewards Program user account) when your personal information may be provided to third parties in ways other than explained above, and you will have the option to prevent such information sharing. 

## Trans-border transfer of your personal information

MyShopping is an Australian entity however our server, and all data we collect in the operation of this site, could be hosted outside of Australia. You understand and agrees that any personal information you provide through your use of this Site may be transferred to our servers ourside of Australia. By continuing to access and use this site, you consent to the application of Australian laws relating to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information and to the transfer of your personal information outside of Australia. 

## Disclosing personal information

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our site. These companies may use information (not personal or contact details) about your visits to this web site to measure advertising effectiveness and to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

## Links to third party sites

MyShopping may contain links to third party sites. These linked sites are not under our control. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites and do not know whether cookies or other tracking devices are used on linked sites. We recommend that you review the privacy policies of each site you visit before disclosing your personal information. 

## Securing your personal information

All personal information held by MyShopping is stored on secure servers that are protected in a controlled environment. You should be aware however that due to the open nature of the Internet, information exchanged via the Internet may be accessed and used by people other than those for whom the data is intended. If you provide or send us any personal information, it is sent at your own risk. Although we endeavour to keep your personal information secure, MyShopping will not be held responsible for any unauthorised access and use of your personal information. To help us keep your personal information secure, you should at all times keep your password, user-name and MyShopping Rewards Program account details used on the MyShopping site confidential. If you become aware of unauthorised usage of your password, user-name or account you should contact us immediately. 

## Privacy changes

To keep this information current and accurate, MyShopping will review and update this Privacy Policy and post the changes here 

## Contact us

Please contact us to find out more about our procedures and policies in relation to the collection, use, disclosure, storage and handling of personal information. 

If at any time you wish to know what information we are holding about you, think we may hold information about you which is incorrect / out of date, you request we delete your personal information, or you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at contactus@MyShopping.com.au. 

If you still require further information then you should contact the (Australian) Office of the Federal Privacy Commissioner whose details follow:  

Phone: Privacy Hotline (in Australia) on 1300-363-992; or  
Web: www.privacy.gov.au  
Post: The Federal Privacy Commissioner, GPO Box 5218, Sydney NSW 1042, Australia  

|
